<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<resources>
	<string name="routes">Routes</string>
	<string name="config">Configuration</string>
	<string name="fitxa">Data Sheet</string>
	<string name="map">Map</string>
	<string name="medals">Medals</string>
	<string name="curses">Races</string>

	<string name="lowAccuracy">You can't start a route if your GPS signal is low or null, you should go to a wider place.</string>
	<string name="nogps">Location is not enabled, you have to enable it.</string>

	<string name="finishButton">Have you finished the route?</string>
	<string name="yes">Yes</string>
	<string name="no">No</string>
	<string name="resetButton">Do you really want to reset the route?</string>
	<string name="pause2back">You need to stop the timer to exit the route.</string>

	<string name="nomCursa1">santantoni</string>
	<string name="nomCursa2">halfmarathon</string>
	<string name="nomCursa3">marathon</string>
	<string name="nomCursa4">firemans</string>
	<string name="nomCursa5">Elcorteingles</string>
	<string name="nomCursa6">lamerce</string>
	<string name="nomCursa7">friendship</string>
	<string name="nomCursa8">womens</string>
	<string name="nomCursa9">JeanBouin</string>
	<string name="nomCursa10">nassos</string>

	<string name="moreInfo">More information: </string>
	<string name="date">Date: </string>

	<string name="meters"> meters</string>

	<string name="data0">January</string>
	<string name="data1">February</string>
	<string name="data2">March</string>
	<string name="data3">April</string>
	<string name="data4">May</string>
	<string name="data5">September</string>
	<string name="data6">November</string>
	<string name="data7">November</string>
	<string name="data8">November</string>
	<string name="data9">December</string>

	<string name="mapData0">2013 Track</string>
	<string name="mapData1">2012 Track</string>
	<string name="mapData2">2013 Track</string>
	<string name="mapData3">2012 Track</string>
	<string name="mapData4">2012 Track</string>
	<string name="mapData5">2012 Track</string>
	<string name="mapData6">2012 Track</string>
	<string name="mapData7">2012 Track</string>
	<string name="mapData8">2012 Track</string>
	<string name="mapData9">2012 Track</string>

	<string name="alert100m">Stop the timer and go back one screen to activate the clock correctly at the start of the route. You are at </string>
	<string name="alert100m2">m from the beginning. To win the medal of the route, the start point and end point must be valid.</string>

	<string name="link0">http://www.cursasantantoni.cat/</string>
	<string name="link1">http://www.mitjabarcelona.com/</string>
	<string name="link2">http://www.zurichmaratobarcelona.es/</string>
	<string name="link3">http://www.cursabombers.com/</string>
	<string name="link4">http://www.cursaelcorteingles.cat/</string>
	<string name="link5">http://www.bcn.cat/cursamerce/</string>
	<string name="link6">http://www.cursadelamistat.com/</string>
	<string name="link7">http://www.carreradelamujer.com/barcelona/</string>
	<string name="link8">http://jeanbouin.mundodeportivo.com/</string>
	<string name="link9">http://www.bcn.cat/cursanassos/</string>

	<string name="alert100mts">alert100m</string>



	<string name="wrongText">Incorrect data. Please, check it.</string>
	<string name="info">With this data we can give you an approximation of ran distance, speed and burnt calories:</string>
	<string name="save">Save</string>
	<string name="reset">Reset</string>
	<string name="age">Age:</string>
	<string name="height">Height (cm):</string>
	<string name="weight">Weight (Kg):</string>

	<string name="based">Aplication based on the book: </string>
	<string name="idea">Original Idea: </string>
	<string name="autor">Authors: </string>
	<string name="fotograf">Photo:</string>
	<string name="dev">Development:</string>
	<string name="done">Done</string>
	<string name="next">Next</string>




	<string name="cursa0text">This is the first big event of the season. If the excesses of Christmas are weighing on you, this is the perfect excuse to begin training in January. Starting next to the market, it goes twice round the neighbourhood, including two long stretches on Gran Via de les Corts Catalanes in the direction of the Besòs. The race has made a name for itself on its own merits and leading Catalan professional athletes usually take part. On the day of the race, there are also races for children of five and up. The main difficulty of the race is the cold at the beginning. Warming up is more necessary than ever and you may have to run in long sleeves to keep your muscles at the right temperature. Every year there’s a long list of entrants, because this is probably the hardest middle-distance race on the local calendar.</string>
	<string name="cursa1text">This is the little sister of the big race and the next step in preparing for the great event, which is held a few weeks later. For most runners it provides a first-rate training opportunity as part of their programme. The organisers have the support of the French company Amaury Sport Organisation, which is also behind mythical competitions like the Tour de France and the Dakar Rally. This helps attract Kenyan stars, who dominate the distance. The weather can be troublesome, with rain, but the temperature is usually mild. The course always runs near the seafront and takes in a lot of the city’s emblematic tourist sites.</string>
	<string name="cursa2text">In 1980 Barcelona joined the list of big cities with their own marathon. It did so by attracting the one that had been organised for the first time two years earlier in Palafrugell. At that first edition, which started from Plaça de Maria Cristina and went round Baix Llobregat, barely 1,000 people enrolled. Since the mid-1990s, the race fully succumbed to the Olympic fever gripping the city. The introduction of the yellow chip in 1995 is still remembered today as the definitive turning point.
In recent years the race has become a world reference. The 4,636 participants in 2006 grew to 15,075 in 2011. the course is quite fast, in spite of the slopes of Diagonal and Passeig de Sant Joan, where you can see the odd grimace of pain. The weather is usually favourable, which means that each year there are more foreign participants, who take advantage of the race to visit the city. The route has been much improved in recent years, which for them is the first sample of the attractions the city has to offer.</string>
	<string name="cursa3text">This is definitely one of the phenomena that has grown parallel to the surge in running in the city. It started as a partnership between Nike and the Barcelona Fire Brigade, with a marketing campaign which over the years has made it one of the challenges not to be missed on the local calendar. At the last edition, the 20,000 places available were taken up within a week. The river of yellow sweatshirts is now a spring classic. In the weeks before the race, the organisers get the entrants together for supervised training sessions, some of them with the presence of top-level athletes. There are also popular night-time sessions, known as the Lunarun. As far as competing goes, the course is extremely fast. Track athletes such as Natalia Rodríguez, Marta Domínguez or Chema Martínez are regulars at this event. In fact, this is the only race in Catalonia to bear the distinction of the Bronze Label of the International Athletics Federation, a label that guarantees quality.</string>
	<string name="cursa4text">The queen of Barcelona races, at least as regards inscriptions. The fact that it’s free has something to do with it, but there’s more to it than that. The Corte Inglés race, thanks to the brand sponsoring it, has become a real institution in its own right. Even in the first edition it drew more than 17,000 runners. Since then it hasn’t stopped growing.
The course isn’t a standard length, but it always fulfils one of its own traditions: the ascent to Montjuïc up Carrer del Foc and the return via the Lluís Companys Olympic Stadium. Your legs will feel the 119 metres of the cumulative ascent, but a lot of people taking part think nothing of slowing down or even walking at some point along the way. This event went down in history in 1994, when 109,457 athletes turned out and established a Guinness world record for a race, which is still standing today. Participation has currently settled around 50,000 to 60,000, a figure that makes it the most popular in the city.</string>
	<string name="cursa5text">The city’s main annual feast day could hardly go by without an athletics meeting. On the occasion of La Mercè, the City Council organises this race on a Sunday morning as the starting signal for the festivities. The course is a 10-kilometre classic with a very demanding stretch near the beginning, with 3,000 metres along Gran Via de les Corts Catalanes. For a lot of people, this is the first race after the holidays. The heat has eased up by now, which encourages a lot of people. All the available places are often taken up, Enrolment costs five euros and the takings go to pay for projects to help handicapped people through sport. The sporting level is high, because the circuit is designed to achieve fast times. In spite of that, it doesn’t go after big international names so as to preserve the traditional festive air of the event.</string>
	<string name="cursa6text">At the beginning of the 1980s, when Barcelona still didn’t have a complete athletics calendar, Francesc Mates decided to organise a race which still stands out above the rest today. He did away with a gap that he felt needed to be filled: a mountain race without leaving the city. Francesc at that time was a key figure in urban athletics in Barcelona. Since 1947 he had been designing sports shoes for runners. He was also one of the driving forces behind the Barcelona Marathon, along with Ramon Oliu. This was how the Friendship Race began life. Every year since 1991 this non-competitive event has commemorated its creator.
It’s a modest race, as it’s still organised by the Mates family through their shoe- making business. Francesc’s daughter Myrna Mates, a skilled shoe-maker and, like her father, an ex-athlete, is now the firm’s visible face. Amongst the sports community the race is known quite simply as the ‘Mates family race’. Being a friendly race, it’s not run with a chip and exact times aren’t measured. In fact, the final classification is always unofficial. Enrolment is free.</string>
	<string name="cursa7text">In the last few years, the growth in participation by women has accounted for a large part of the exponential increase in inscriptions in all the races contested in the city. Between 20 and 25% of people taking part are women. But one Sunday in October they are the ones in charge in the street.
This race is also part of the national circuit, but it also has links to Woman’s Sports Week, seven days during which admission to municipal facilities and sports classes is free. Inscription for the race is by payment, but part of it goes to the Spanish Cancer Association. This pledge means there is no lack of well-known faces, like María Vasco or Érika Villaécija. There is a predominantly festive atmosphere. The event has been an undisputed success with the women of Barcelona and in five years inscriptions have multiplied by five. For a lot of the women, this is an initial race that hooks them for others.</string>
	<string name="cursa8text">No matter how many races there are on the local calendar, none is as old- established as the Jean Bouin. On 1 February 1920, 48 pioneers lined up at the start of the first edition, in Esplugues de Llobregat. The winner that day was Rossend Calvet, with an excellent time of 34’ 10”. Nine decades later, the Jean Bouin is the grand old man of Spanish athletics races, with an almost unbroken history. The race is held in memory of an athlete from Marseille who died in 1914 on a First World War battlefield. Two years earlier, he had won the silver medal for the 5,000 metres at the Stockholm Olympics, earning himself a host of followers.
At the first editions the public was already behind the brave runners and poured into the street to cheer them on. With this backing, the Jean Bouin went on to new breakthroughs, in 1946 it was opened up to foreign athletes and the following year to women. In 1987 it added a category for wheelchairs and in 2005 for transplant patients.
In 1979 the race was definitively extended to citizens when it was made open to everybody. At the beginning of the 21st century, participation figures brushed the 1,000 mark, but within a few years it had made an enormous leap. The present circuit, which is almost identical to the 1973 circuit, begins with a long stretch along Gran Via de les Corts Catalanes and ends with a steep, 50-metre climb on Montjuïc. The morning chill of autumn complicates the experience, but don’t hesitate to take part in an incomparable story.</string>
	<string name="cursa9text">Between your Christmas dinner and New Year’s Eve toasts, the last afternoon of December offers an opportunity to see the year out burning calories. The Saint Sylvester tradition began in 1925 in São Paulo, where the weather at this time of year lends itself to running more than it does here. In Barcelona it has taken the name L’Home dels Nassos (‘The man with the noses’), a character with ‘as many noses as the day has years’, who children are told to look for on the last day of the year.
The course is extremely fast and runs along the coast with hardly any slopes. This race has seen such impressive times as the Spanish record set by the athlete Rosa Morató from Navarcles. The race ends after sundown, which is unusual in amateur competitions, but participation nevertheless goes up year after year. The route makes for a festive atmosphere as an appetiser for New Year’s Eve dinner, where you can tell everyone all about your race.</string>

	<string name="free">Free</string>

	<string name="correct">Correct</string>
	<string name="incorrect">Incorrect</string>

	<string name="initPoint">Start Point:</string>
	<string name="finalPoint">End Point:</string>
	<string name="timeLabel">Time:</string>
	<string name="distanceLabel">Distance:</string>
	<string name="velocityLabel">Average pace:</string>
	<string name="calorieLabel">Energy:</string>
	<string name="medalLabel">Achieved Medals:</string>

	<string name="distance">Distance:</string>
	<string name="sign">Signposting:</string>
	<string name="terrain">Surface:</string>
	<string name="day">Day/Night:</string>
	<string name="desP">Net ascent:</string>
	<string name="desA">Total cumulative ascent:</string>
	<string name="espV">Green zones:</string>
	<string name="water">Drinking fountains:</string>
	<string name="time">Time:</string>
	<string name="dif">Difficulty:</string>
	
	<string name="pollen">Pollen</string>

	<string name="medalBarTitle1">BCN Corre Routes</string>
	<string name="medalBarColor1">white</string>

	<string name="medalBarTitle2">BCN Corre Races</string>
	<string name="medalBarColor2">#F8B905</string>
	
	<string name="medalBarTitle3">Distance</string>
	<string name="medalBarColor3">#00A096</string>
	
	<string name="medalBarTitle4">Speed</string>
	<string name="medalBarColor4">#DF2477</string>
	
	<string name="medalBarTitle5">Calories</string>
	<string name="medalBarColor5">#E75F15</string>
	
	<string name="medalBarTitle6">Number of routes completed this month</string>
	<string name="medalBarColor6">#93107D</string>

	<string name="distance1">4800 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign1">Montjuïc Castle sports circuit</string>
	<string name="terrain1">ASPHALT AND GRAVEL</string>
	<string name="day1">DAY</string>
	<string name="desP1">149 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA1">168 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV1">images/niveles/nivelbosque3.png</string>
	<string name="water1">images/niveles/nivelfuentes1.png</string>
	<string name="time1">50 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif1">HIGH</string>
	<string name="dif_image1">images/niveles/niveldificultad8.png</string>

	<string name="distance2">6000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign2">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain2">ASPHALT AND GRAVEL</string>
	<string name="day2">MORNING AND AFTERNOON</string>
	<string name="desP2">0 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA2">22 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV2">images/niveles/nivelbosque1.png</string>
	<string name="water2">images/niveles/nivelfuentes1.png</string>
	<string name="time2">40 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif2">MEDIUM</string>
	<string name="dif_image2">images/niveles/niveldificultad5.png</string>

	<string name="distance3">6000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign3">Av. Diagonal sports circuit</string>
	<string name="terrain3">ASPHALT AND GRAVEL</string>
	<string name="day3">MORNING AND AFTERNOON</string>
	<string name="desP3">0 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA3">89 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV3">images/niveles/nivelbosque2.png</string>
	<string name="water3">images/niveles/nivelfuentes1.png</string>
	<string name="time3">45 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif3">MEDIUM-LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image3">images/niveles/niveldificultad4.png</string>

	<string name="distance4">6000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign4">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain4">ASPHALT AND GRAVEL</string>
	<string name="day4">MORNING AND AFTERNOON</string>
	<string name="desP4">0 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA4">89 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV4">images/niveles/nivelbosque2.png</string>
	<string name="water4">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time4">50 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif4">LOW-MEDIUM</string>
	<string name="dif_image4">images/niveles/niveldificultad4.png</string>

	<string name="distance5">4800 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign5">Sports circuits of Rambla de Prim and Diagonal-Sant Martí</string>
	<string name="terrain5">ASPHALT</string>
	<string name="day5">24 HOURS</string>
	<string name="desP5">0 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA5">6,3 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV5">images/niveles/nivelbosque2.png</string>
	<string name="water5">images/niveles/nivelfuentes1.png</string>
	<string name="time5">30 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif5">LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image5">images/niveles/niveldificultad2.png</string>

	<string name="distance6">5300 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign6">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain6">ASPHALT, GRAVEL AND GRASS</string>
	<string name="day6">DAY</string>
	<string name="desP6">95 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA6">157 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV6">images/niveles/nivelbosque3.png</string>
	<string name="water6">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time6">45 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif6">MEDIUM</string>
	<string name="dif_image6">images/niveles/niveldificultad5.png</string>

	<string name="distance7">5200 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign7">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain7">ASPHALT AND GRAVEL</string>
	<string name="day7">MORNING AND AFTERNOON</string>
	<string name="desP7">99.7 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA7">137 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV7">images/niveles/nivelbosque3.png</string>
	<string name="water7">images/niveles/nivelfuentes3.png</string>
	<string name="time7">50 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif7">HIGH</string>
	<string name="dif_image7">images/niveles/niveldificultad8.png</string>

	<string name="distance8">5800 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign8">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain8">ASPHALT, GRAVEL, PAVING AND GRASS</string>
	<string name="day8">24 HOURS</string>
	<string name="desP8">68.5 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA8">96.7 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV8">images/niveles/nivelbosque2.png</string>
	<string name="water8">images/niveles/nivelfuentes1.png</string>
	<string name="time8">50 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif8">HIGH</string>
	<string name="dif_image8">images/niveles/niveldificultad8.png</string>

	<string name="distance9">7000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign9">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain9">ASPHALT</string>
	<string name="day9">MORNING AND AFTERNOON</string>
	<string name="desP9">0 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA9">164 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV9">images/niveles/nivelbosque2.png</string>
	<string name="water9">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time9">60 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif9">MEDIUM-HIGH</string>
	<string name="dif_image9">images/niveles/niveldificultad7.png</string>

	<string name="distance10">6300 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign10">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain10">ASPHALT, GRAVEL AND GRASS</string>
	<string name="day10">MORNING AND AFTERNOON</string>
	<string name="desP10">141 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA10">301 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV10">images/niveles/nivelbosque4.png</string>
	<string name="water10">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time10">60 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif10">HIGH</string>
	<string name="dif_image10">images/niveles/niveldificultad8.png</string>

	<string name="distance11">7000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign11">Sports circuit of the Parc de la Ciutadella</string>
	<string name="terrain11">ASPHALT, GRAVEL AND GRASS</string>
	<string name="day11">10 AM - NIGHTFALL</string>
	<string name="desP11">2.1 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA11">0 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV11">images/niveles/nivelbosque3.png</string>
	<string name="water11">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time11">40 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif11">LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image11">images/niveles/niveldificultad2.png</string>

	<string name="distance12">5200 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign12">Passeig Marítim sports circuit</string>
	<string name="terrain12">ASPHALT, GRAVEL AND GRASS</string>
	<string name="day12">DAY AND NIGHT</string>
	<string name="desP12">0 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA12">8 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV12">images/niveles/nivelbosque3.png</string>
	<string name="water12">images/niveles/nivelfuentes4.png</string>
	<string name="time12">30 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif12">LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image12">images/niveles/niveldificultad2.png</string>

	<string name="distance13">5300 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign13">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain13">ASPHALT AND GRAVEL</string>
	<string name="day13">10 PM - NIGHTFALL</string>
	<string name="desP13">-23.4 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA13">13 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV13">images/niveles/nivelbosque2.png</string>
	<string name="water13">images/niveles/nivelfuentes4.png</string>
	<string name="time13">60 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif13">MEDIUM-LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image13">images/niveles/niveldificultad3.png</string>

	<string name="distance14">4100 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign14">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain14">ASPHALT</string>
	<string name="day14">MORNINGS (very early)</string>
	<string name="desP14">0 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA14">22 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV14">images/niveles/nivelbosque1.png</string>
	<string name="water14">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time14">30 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif14">LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image14">images/niveles/niveldificultad2.png</string>

	<string name="distance15">6000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign15">Can Dragó sports circuit</string>
	<string name="terrain15">ASPHALT AND SAND</string>
	<string name="day15">MORNINGS AND AFTERNOONS</string>
	<string name="desP15">-40 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA15">4 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV15">images/niveles/nivelbosque2.png</string>
	<string name="water15">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time15">20 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif15">LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image15">images/niveles/niveldificultad2.png</string>

	<string name="distance16">5000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign16">Joan Miró sports circuit</string>
	<string name="terrain16">ASPHALT, SAND AND GRASS</string>
	<string name="day16">ALL DAY (while there’s light)</string>
	<string name="desP16">80 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA16">100 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV16">images/niveles/nivelbosque3.png</string>
	<string name="water16">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time16">40 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif16">MEDIUM-HIGH</string>
	<string name="dif_image16">images/niveles/niveldificultad7.png</string>


	<string name="perfil">Profile</string>
	<string name="infoProfile">Info</string>


	<string name="distance17">8000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign17">ROUTE 100% SIGNPOSTED</string>
	<string name="terrain17">EARTH</string>
	<string name="day17">MORNINGS AND AFTERNOONS</string>
	<string name="desP17">14 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA17">43 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV17">images/niveles/nivelbosque4.png</string>
	<string name="water17">images/niveles/nivelfuentes3.png</string>
	<string name="time17">45 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif17">LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image17">images/niveles/niveldificultad2.png</string>

	<string name="distance18">3500 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign18">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain18">SAND AND ASPHALT</string>
	<string name="day18">ALL DAY (while there’s daylight)</string>
	<string name="desP18">110 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA18">117 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV18">images/niveles/nivelbosque3.png</string>
	<string name="water18">images/niveles/nivelfuentes3.png</string>
	<string name="time18">30 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif18">HIGH</string>
	<string name="dif_image18">images/niveles/niveldificultad8.png</string>

	<string name="distance19">7000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign19">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain19">EARTH</string>
	<string name="day19">MORNINGS</string>
	<string name="desP19">0 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA19">181 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV19">images/niveles/nivelbosque4.png</string>
	<string name="water19">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time19">50 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif19">MEDIUM-HIGH</string>
	<string name="dif_image19">images/niveles/niveldificultad7.png</string>

	<string name="distance20">3500 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign20">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain20">ASPHALT</string>
	<string name="day20">MORNINGS</string>
	<string name="desP20">88.7 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA20">88.7 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV20">images/niveles/nivelbosque1.png</string>
	<string name="water20">images/niveles/nivelfuentes1.png</string>
	<string name="time20">40 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif20">MEDIUM</string>
	<string name="dif_image20">images/niveles/niveldificultad.png</string>


	<string name="distance21">9000 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign21">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain21">GRASS AND PAVING</string>
	<string name="day21">MORNINGS AND AFTERNOONS (while there’s daylight)</string>
	<string name="desP21">20 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA21">20 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV21">images/niveles/nivelbosque4.png</string>
	<string name="water21">images/niveles/nivelfuentes1.png</string>
	<string name="time21">50 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif21">LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image21">images/niveles/niveldificultad2.png</string>

	<string name="distance22">6500 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign22">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain22">ASPHALT</string>
	<string name="day22">MORNINGS AND AFTERNOONS</string>
	<string name="desP22">-2 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA22">20 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV22">images/niveles/nivelbosque1.png</string>
	<string name="water22">images/niveles/nivelfuentes1.png</string>
	<string name="time22">40 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif22">LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image22">images/niveles/niveldificultad2.png</string>

	<string name="distance23">5200 METRES</string>
	<string name="sign23">NO</string>
	<string name="terrain23">ASPHALT</string>
	<string name="day23">NIGHT</string>
	<string name="desP23">16 METRES</string>
	<string name="desA23">29 METRES</string>
	<string name="espV23">images/niveles/nivelbosque1.png</string>
	<string name="water23">images/niveles/nivelfuentes2.png</string>
	<string name="time23">30 MINUTES</string>
	<string name="dif23">LOW</string>
	<string name="dif_image23">images/niveles/niveldificultad2.png</string>

	<string name="cursa0">The Sant Antoni neighbourhood race</string>
	<string name="cursa1">Half marathon</string>
	<string name="cursa2">Marathon</string>
	<string name="cursa3">Firemen’s race</string>
	<string name="cursa4">The Corte Inglés race</string>
	<string name="cursa5">The Mercè race</string>
	<string name="cursa6">Friendship race</string>
	<string name="cursa7">Women’s Race</string>
	<string name="cursa8">Jean Bouin</string>
	<string name="cursa9">Cursa dels Nassos</string>
	<string name="rutasdistritos">ROUTES BY DISTRICTS</string>
	<string name="route1">Past, present and future of the Olympic Mountain</string>
	<string name="route1bot">Plaça d'Espanya – Olympic Stadium – Montjuïc Castle</string>
	<string name="route2">San Andreu full steam ahead</string>
	<string name="route2bot">Plaça d'Orfila -  La Maquinista - Ronda Litoral - Plaça d'Orfila</string>
	<string name="route3">Les Corts, red and blue (blaugrana) and green</string>
	<string name="route3bot">Parc Maternitat - Parc Castell de l'Oreneta - Parc de Cervantes</string>
	<string name="route4">Fly over the ring road</string>
	<string name="route4bot">Horta Cycle Track – Parc del Castell de l’Oreneta – Parc de Cervantes</string>
	<string name="route5">The athletes' Fòrum</string>
	<string name="route5bot">Rambla de Prim - Fòrum - Plaça de les Glòries</string>
	<string name="route6">Winding up to the Cycle Track</string>
	<string name="route6bot">El Congrés neighbourhood - Turó de la Peira - Horta Cycle Track</string>
	<string name="route7">Running is Modernista</string>
	<string name="route7bot">Sagrada Família - Hospital de Sant Pau - Parc del Guinardó</string>
	<string name="route8">Going up to the Font del Gat</string>
	<string name="route8bot">Parc de les Cascades - Moll de la Fusta - Miramar - Font del Gat</string>
	<string name="route9">A first category climb</string>
	<string name="route9bot">Via Favència - Torre Baró - Via Júlia - Parc de la Guineueta</string>
	<string name="route10">The three hills</string>
	<string name="route10bot">Turó del Putget - Parc Güell - Turó del Carmel - Parc del Guinardó</string>
	<string name="rutastematicas">THEMED ROUTES</string>
	<string name="route11">Parks and gardens</string>
	<string name="route11bot">Diagonal Mar - Carles I - Ciutadella</string>
	<string name="route12">Cold days</string>
	<string name="route12bot">Hotel Vela - Nova Icària -  Fòrum</string>
	<string name="route13">City block interiors</string>
	<string name="route13bot">Palau Robert - Calàbria - Plaça de la Universitat</string>
	<string name="route14">Feast days</string>
	<string name="route14bot">Plaça de Catalunya - Plaça de Sant Jaume - Estació de França</string>
	<string name="route15">Beginners</string>
	<string name="route15bot">Can Dragó - Plaça de les Glòries - Arc de Triomf</string>
	<string name="route16">The athlete's Montjuïc</string>
	<string name="route16bot">Parc de Joan Miró - Joan Serrahima stadium- Mirador del Migdia</string>
	<string name="route17">The all-time classic: Carretera de les Aigües</string>
	<string name="route17bot">Pla dels Maduixers - Vallvidrera - Sant Pere Màrtir</string>
	<string name="route18">The old municipalities</string>
	<string name="route18bot">Sarrià - Parc de Joan Raventós - Vallvidrera</string>
	<string name="rutasrepte">ROUTES WITH A CHALLENGE</string>
	<string name="route19">Hill running</string>
	<string name="route19bot">Vallvidrera - La Budellera - Vallvidrera reservoir</string>
	<string name="route20">From the shoreline to Sarrià</string>
	<string name="route20bot">Jardins de les Tres Xemeneies- Entença - Sarrià</string>
	<string name="route21">Going upriver</string>
	<string name="route21bot">Bon Pastor - Besòs - Vallbona</string>
	<string name="route22">Just one street</string>
	<string name="route22bot">Plaça de les Glòries - Passeig de Gràcia - Plaça de Cerdà</string>
	<string name="route23">Running by night</string>
	<string name="route23bot">Travessera de les Corts  - Travessera de Gràcia - Plaça d'en Joanic</string>
	<string name="rutaLliure">FREE ROUTE</string>
	<string name="route24">Barcelona on demand</string>
	<string name="rutaLliureText">With this option you can make your own route.</string>
</resources>